we're looking at the rock 64 today this
今天这 64我们看到的岩石
is from pine sixty-four you remember
是你记得的松树六十四
them from last week's show we looked at
他们从上周的节目中看到了我们
the a 64
一个64
LTS now this week we're looking at this
LTS现在本周我们正在考虑这个问题
credit card-sized board so half the size
信用卡 大小的板，一半大小
easily and pretty close to the size of a
容易和非常接近的大小
raspberry pi I would say we're gonna
树莓派我 会说我们会的
find out when I measure it there
找出我在那里测量的时间
this one is should we just get into the
这个是我们应该进入的
box yes because this is an unboxing
框是的，因为这是一个拆箱
right I'll talk while I unbox here we go
我在这里打开时会说话，我们会去
so it kind of actually has a reminiscent
所以它实际上有一种让人想起的东西
look to a Raspberry Pi if you will let's
如果你愿意的话，看看Raspberry Pi吧
get in here the rock 64 is are you ready
进入这里摇滚64是你准备好了吗？
for this sash I am 4k 60 frames per
对于这个窗框，我是 每个 4k 60帧
second it's got full-sized HDMI we've
第二，我们有全尺寸HDMI
got an AV port there we've got gigabit
我们有一个AV端口，我们有千兆位
ethernet Wow okay this has got a 4 core
以太网 哇好吧 这个有 4核
processor it's the arm cortex a53 64-bit
处理器它的臂皮质a53 64位
processor and are you ready I keep
处理器和你准备好了吗 我一直
saying I'm excited about this sash this
说我对这条 腰带 感到很兴奋
one comes in three different models they
一个有三种不同的型号
all look pretty much the same but there
看起来都几乎 相同 ，但有
is a one gig model which would put it on
是一个可以穿上它的演出模型
par memory wise so I'm talking about the
票面内存明智的，所以我说 的是
RAM here we put it on par with the
RAM这里我们把它看齐 的
Raspberry Pi 3 B+ as far as the memory
Raspberry Pi 3 B + 至于记忆
goes there's a 2 gig model which puts it
去那里是一个2 gig模型， 它
on par as far as the capacity of the
就能力而言
memory goes with say and xu 4 and there
记忆随着说和xu 4 而去
is a 4 gigabyte model
是一个4千兆字节的型号
it's ddr3 1600 megahertz Ram and let's
它是ddr3 1600兆赫拉姆让我们
get a look at the board itself here so
看看这里的电路板本身
we've got a microSD port at the bottom
我们底部有一个microSD端口
here this is for your micro SD card
这是给你的micro SD 卡
which is pretty traditional for these
这对于这些非常传统
small single board computers I've got
我有小型单板电脑
the 4 gig model yes and then on this
4 gig模型是，然后在此
side once again we end up with an emmc
再一次，我们最终得到了一个emmc
partly MMC interface so that again is a
部分MMC界面再次是一个
different type of storage from the micro
来自微观的不同类型的存储
sd it's more reliable it's faster and
sd它更可靠，速度更快
it's just a chip that we
它只是我们的芯片
can snap right onto the board there and
可以直接卡在板上
this device already has Android 7.1
这个设备已经安装了 Android 7.1
available for it it's got a Debian
可用的它有一个Debian
installation that's available for it
安装可用于它
octo which I haven't seen and a lot more
octo，我 还没有看到，还有更多
coming now this is a brand new board so
现在来，这是一个 全新的董事会
we're gonna see a lot of distributions
我们会看到很多发行版
coming out on this over the next little
走出这个 在 未来的 小
while it has you can see a couple of
同时， 它拥有你可以看到一对夫妇 的
different GPIO s here so we've got the
不同的 GPIO在这里，所以我们得到 了
the pi 2 bus we've got the PI p5 plus
在 PI 2路公交车，我们已经得到了PI P5 加
bus we've got you move that a little bit
我们已经有了总线您移动一点点
closer to the ruler just for me you want
你想要的更接近统治者
me to see yes am I out of the frame a
我看是 我是 出帧 的
little bit GPIO there thanks Sasha okay
有点GPIO那里谢谢Sasha 好吧
I can't see it like you see it I'm
我看不到它就像你看到 我一样
seeing this live and I want to bring it
看到这个现场 ，我想 带来它
closer to me okay we've got USB 2.0
离我越来越近我们有USB 2.0
we've got two of those we've got one
我们有两个那些 我们已经有了 一个
blue one what do you think the blue
蓝色你觉得 蓝色 怎么样？
stands for that's a USB 3 port my
代表我的USB 3端口
friends I already mentioned Gigabit
朋友我 已经提到过千兆
Ethernet and of course just like you
以太网当然和你一样
would expect with the GPIO that's
期待与 GPIO的关系
available on this board we can do all
可在 此板上 我们能做到
kinds of things with this if you're a
如果你是一个这样 的事情
maker if you want to add some sensors to
制造商， 如果你想添加一些传感器
it or other devices connected to this
它或与此相关的其他设备
device you can do that I've got a couple
你可以做的设备，我有一对
of other cool little things here first
其他很酷 的 小东西在这里第一次
of all on board we have a power and
在船上，我们 有一个力量和
reset button that's built right into the
重置按钮，内置于
to the circuit board here and there's
到这里 和那里的 电路 板
also a restore button as well and once
还有一个恢复按钮和一次
again oh before I get to the barrel Jack
再来哦， 在我到达桶 杰克之前
this is kind of interesting this looks
这 是很有趣，这看起来
cool we've got the infrared sensor built
清凉我们已经有了 内置 的红外传感器
right in as well and over here is the
就在这里，在这里是
barrel Jack that's a three point three
桶杰克，这是 三分之 三
point five millimeter barrel connector
点五毫米桶连接器
which is incidentally the same as the
这是偶然的
one that we've reviewed in the past so
我们过去 回顾过的那个
five volts three amp and that's going to
五伏三安培 ，这将是
take it just like that so that's where
把它就是这样 ，这样的 地方
you get your power from there's no micro
你从那里得到你的 力量 没有 微观
USB to be finicky or anything like that
USB很挑剔或类似的东西
what do you think that I love it
你 觉得 我喜欢它 怎么样？
beautiful not a lot more that I can tell
美丽不是很多，我可以告诉
you on an unboxing video but it looks
你是一个拆箱视频，但看起来
well built I'm excited about it
精心打造 我很 兴奋
gonna heatsink I'm gonna put on it let's
要散热片我要穿上它 ，让我们
get the measurements for you how am I in
得到你的测量结果我是怎么进去的
the frame good now
现在 的 框架好
fantastic all right this way we've got
我们这样做很棒
five and a half inches that can't be
五英寸半不能
right what is it what are these
这是什么， 这是什么
measurements a she took one crazy ruler
测量她 带了一个疯狂的统治者
Ravi that is one crazy ruler maybe there
Ravi 可能 是一个疯狂的统治者
we go bring it a little bit it's like
我们带点它 就像
not metric bring it up yeah there we go
不是公制 提出来的，是的，我们去了
that'll be zero okay two inches I'm like
这将是 零毫米，我想是两英寸
that is not five inches
那不是 五英寸
Wow two inches and three millimeters
哇两英寸三毫米
four millimeters give or take this way I
四毫米给我或采取这种 方式我
don't know what measurements these are
不知道这是什么测量
I'm gonna have to look at this out there
我就不得不 在 这 看 出来有
maybe it's like some like we work in
也许就像我们工作的一样
metric this is all oh yeah its
公制，这是哦，是的
centimeters cool and this way we are one
厘米很酷，这样我们就是一个
two three and a quarter inches and maybe
两个三又四分之一 英寸， 也许
a millimeter or two there you go so
你去的那一毫米或者两毫米
roughly the same size as a Raspberry Pi
大小与Raspberry Pi大致相同
three in this box here I've got a nice
这个盒子里有三个 我很高兴
little case for it can these devices be
这些设备可以用于它的小案例
powered over p OE this one i don't
我不知道 这个
believe has p OE as a matter of fact but
相信 事实上是有效的，但是
you could i suppose do a p OE splitter
你可以 想 我 做一个 分配器
you can buy a splitter that has the
你可以买到具有分路器
correct barrel adapter and power it that
正确的桶适配器并为其供电
way so we've got these kind of risers at
方式，使我们有这几样提升装置中 的
once again similar kind of design to
再次类似的设计
ones we've looked at in the past from
那些我们已经在过去打量起
pine sixty-four so the board is gonna go
松六十四，所以董事会将去
right on there and we've got the riser
就在那里 ， 我们 有了立管
that goes up there and then the plexi
那里上升然后是树丛
with the rock 64 logo this time goes
随着摇滚64标志的出现
right up there there you have it so
在那里，你有它
sharp beautiful I can't wait to fire
锋利的美丽我迫不及待地开火
that one up as well we're gonna we're
那一个我们就是我们要的
gonna have to put these things
必须把这些东西
head-to-head and this one with 4k 60p
头对头，这个与4k 60p
and a very nice processor and four gigs
和一个非常好的处理器和 四个演出
of ram and emmc and USB three we're
ram和emmc 以及USB 三我们是
going to need to put some games on there
需要在那里放一些游戏
as well and see how it performs with
同时也 看看它是如何表现的
retropie or something like that
retropie或类似的东西
now we are going to need if you want
现在我们将需要你
bluetooth for controllers or something
蓝牙 控制器或其他东西
like that you're going to need a
就像 那样你 需要 一个
bluetooth dongle or possibly a Wi-Fi
蓝牙加密狗或可能是Wi-Fi
dongle if you want to get it on Wi-Fi
加密狗，如果你想在Wi-Fi上获得它
instead of using Gigabit Ethernet but
而不是 使用千兆以太网
this is a great looking maker board
这是一个很棒的制造商董事会
can't wait to fire her up
我等不及她了
[Music]
[音乐]
[Applause]
[掌声]